Yumi's Cells 2
유미의 세포들 2
Episode 1 Cool Goodbyes
에피소드 1 안녕히 계세요
End the relationship
관계를 끝내세요
Yumi
유미
I thought about it a lot
많은 생각을 했어요
and I think we should end it here.
내 생각엔 여기서 끝내야 할 것 같아.
All right, we should.
좋아, 그래야 해.
I feel the same.
나도 같은 느낌이다.
Where are you going?
어디 가세요?
I have to stop by somewhere.
어딘가에 들러야 해요.
I'll get going then.
그럼 바로 갈게요.
All right.
괜찮은.
Is the end like this?
끝은 이렇지?
There isn't anything more?
더 이상 아무것도 없나요?
The end? Is that the real end?
끝? 그게 진짜 끝인가요?
Is this where it ends?
여기서 끝나는 걸까요?
He left. He really left.
그는 떠났다. 그는 정말로 떠났다.
Then can Yumi go home now too?
그럼 이제 유미도 집에 갈 수 있을까요?
But did it really end like that? As if it were nothing?
그런데 정말 그렇게 끝났나요? 마치 아무것도 아닌 것처럼?
Yes, it's the end.
예, 끝입니다.
Mailman.
우편 집배원.
It's over. The end.
끝났습니다. 끝.
Here, take this.
여기, 이것을 가져가세요.
What's that ?
그게 뭐죠?
Notice of Breakup.
해체 통지.
If Love receives this, the relationship has officially ended.
사랑이 이것을 받으면 관계는 공식적으로 종료됩니다.
Wait, Love cell is on the ambulance right now.
잠깐만요, 러브셀은 지금 구급차에 있어요.
Love!
사랑!
Then someone give this to Love–
그럼 누군가 이것을 Love에게 주세요–
Then Reason, you accept it instead.
그렇다면 이유, 당신이 대신 그것을 받아들입니다.
Me? Why me? I'm in charge of reason.
나? 왜 나야? 나는 이성을 담당한다.
You have to take it now, there's no time.
지금 가져 가야합니다. 시간이 없습니다.
No, it's not even my responsibility. Why would you give it to me?
아니, 그건 내 책임도 아니다. 왜 나한테 주려고 했어?
Someone has to accept it.
누군가는 그것을 받아들여야 합니다.
I don't know.
모르겠습니다.
Where are you going?
어디 가세요?
You guys! You have to accept the breakup notice
여러분! 이별 통보를 받아들여야 해
so that the relationship officially ends!
그래서 관계가 공식적으로 종료됩니다!
This is not something you can avoid!
이것은 피할 수 있는 것이 아닙니다!
If you avoid this now, a bigger problem will happen!
지금 이것을 피하면 더 큰 문제가 발생할 것입니다!
You guys! Where did you go?
여러분! 어디로 갔나요?
♫ I think I missed it again, Your heart ♫
♫ 또 놓쳤나 봐 너의 마음 ♫
♫ I think our time has gotten farther away ♫
♫ 우리의 시간은 점점 멀어진 것 같아요 ♫
♫ Even if I try to look back ♫
♫ 돌아보려 해도 ♫
Come to think of it,
생각해 보니,
When I think about it,
생각해 보면,
Wung must have been angry about something he was disappointed about.
Wung은 자신이 실망한 것에 대해 화를 냈을 것입니다.
Angry?
화난?
You saw it earlier. People can't be that calm when they are breaking up.
아까 보셨잖아요. 사람들은 헤어질 때 그렇게 침착할 수 없습니다.
Then are you saying he was trying to see what Yumi was going to do?
그럼 유미가 뭘 할지 보려고 했다는 건가요?
That could have been possible.
그것은 가능할 수도 있었습니다.
I don't think so.
나는 그렇게 생각하지 않습니다.
They both liked each other.
그들은 둘 다 서로를 좋아했습니다.
What if Wung is waiting for Yumi to hold onto him?
Wung이 Yumi가 자신을 붙잡기를 기다리고 있다면 어떻게 될까요?
Do you think so?
그렇게 생각하시나요?
Pathetic, that's enough.
한심하다, 그것으로 충분하다.
I think this is too pathetic.
나는 이것이 너무 한심하다고 생각한다.
- What is... - Where are you going?
- 그게 뭐야... - 어디 가세요?
Mailman.
우편 집배원.
I will take it. I think I'm the only one who can accept the breakup notice.
내가 가져갈게. 이별 통보를 받아들일 수 있는 사람은 나뿐인 것 같다.
I'm glad you came around. I can go home now.
당신이 와줘서 기뻐요. 이제 집에 갈 수 있어요.
But... I'll accept it tomorrow morning with a clear head.
하지만... 내일 아침에는 맑은 머리로 받아들이겠습니다.
What? Why?
무엇? 왜?
Breaking up is a big deal.
헤어지는 것은 큰 일입니다.
Yumi needs to rest now.
유미는 이제 쉬어야 해요.
♫ Today too because my day ♫
♫ 오늘도 내 하루니까 ♫
♫ approaches slowly, ♫
♫ 천천히 다가온다, ♫
♫ I didn't even expect this ♫
♫ 난 이런 걸 기대하지도 않았어 ♫
♫ he is playing a joke ♫
♫ 그는 농담을 하고 있어요 ♫
♫ Why of all days this morning ♫
♫ 왜 오늘 아침엔 ♫
♫ without any preparation ♫
♫ 아무 준비도 없이 ♫
I'll just
그냥
pretend it didn't happen.
그런 일이 일어나지 않은 척.
Yes, I'll do that.
네, 그렇게 하겠습니다.
I'll tell him I was a little harsh.
내가 좀 가혹했다고 그에게 말할게요.
That I didn't mean it.
그런 뜻은 아니었어요.
Wung will understand.
웅은 이해할 것이다.
♫ To me who am spending an unexpected day ♫
♫ 뜻밖의 하루를 보내고 있는 나에게 ♫
I'll go to Wung's place right now.
나는 지금 당장 웅의 집으로 갈 것이다.
Yumi, what are you doing now?
유미 씨, 지금 뭐 해요?
Do you not hear me? What are you doing?
내 말 안 들려? 뭐하세요?
Hang up right now!
지금 당장 끊으세요!
Do you not have any pride?
자존심은 없나요?
You decided to break up!
헤어지기로 결정했어요!
What are you doing right now?!
지금 뭐하세요?!
Get out of here!
여기서 나가세요!
I don't care! Forget pride!
난 상관없어! 자존심은 잊어라!
I just want to go back to the way things were with Wung!
나는 단지 Wung과의 관계로 돌아가고 싶습니다!
Wung could be waiting for us to call!
Wung은 우리가 전화하기를 기다리고 있을지도 모릅니다!
How much more pathetic are you going to make Yumi be?
유미를 얼마나 더 한심하게 만들 셈이냐?
Seriously, these guys!
진심이야, 이놈들아!
Guys stop it.
얘들아 그만해
Stop it!
그만해요!
I don't want to break up. I don't need pride!
나는 헤어지고 싶지 않다. 자존심은 필요없어!
Wung! Your call cannot be connected. You will be connected to voicemail.
웅! 통화를 연결할 수 없습니다. 음성 메일로 연결됩니다.
Please leave a message after the beep.
삐 소리가 난 후 메시지를 남겨주세요.
You can't!
당신은 할 수 없습니다!
How about it? Does it feel real now?
어때요? 이제 현실이 느껴지나요?
This is real. Hurry up and accept it.
이것은 진짜입니다. 서둘러서 받아들이세요.
Let's admit it.
인정하자.
It's over.
끝났습니다.
Wung
웅
Delete
삭제
Do you want to transfer the contact to the trash? Yes
연락처를 휴지통으로 이동하시겠습니까? 예
Even though I am older, storms are still scary.
나이가 들었지만 폭풍은 여전히 ​​무섭습니다.
But one thing is different.
하지만 한 가지는 다릅니다.
Now I don't want to be swept away helplessly by the storm.
이제는 폭풍에 무력하게 휩쓸리고 싶지 않습니다.
Everyone hold tight! We must not lose any cell.
다들 꽉 잡으세요! 우리는 어떤 세포도 잃어서는 안 됩니다.
Change seats with me. This seat is scary!
나랑 자리 바꿔요. 이 자리는 무섭다!
You should have told me before we got on.
우리가 타기 전에 나한테 말했어야 했는데.
Guys, let's keep holding on! We have to be different now!
얘들아, 계속 버티자! 이제 우리는 달라져야 해요!
♫ Let's put behind us our weary hearts and think about someone ♫
♫ 지친 마음을 뒤로하고 누군가에 대해 생각해보자 ♫
Yumi is an adult now.
유미는 이제 성인이 되었습니다.
Let's part ways in a cool manner, please!
쿨하게 헤어지자 제발!
♫ In the times which I always spent the same way crying ♫
♫ 늘 같은 시간을 울며 보내던 시간에 ♫
I don't want to send her out looking terrible just because they broke up!
헤어졌다는 이유만으로 그녀를 끔찍한 모습으로 보내고 싶지 않아요!
I don't want to walk around with sunken eyes from staying up all night!
밤을 새워서 움푹 들어간 눈으로 돌아다니고 싶지 않아요!
Let's not look like a weak person who broke down because of love!
사랑 때문에 무너진 약한 사람처럼 보이지 말자!
Oh! Assistant Manager Yumi!
오! 유미 대리!
Oh.
오.
Good morning.
좋은 아침이에요.
Good morning, did you have a good weekend?
좋은 아침이에요, 주말 잘 보내셨나요?
- You must have worked hard preparing for the meeting. - Yes.
- 회의 준비하느라 고생하셨을 텐데요. - 예.
Did you see the material for today's meeting?
오늘 회의 자료는 보셨나요?
Yes. I like the new planning report.
예. 새로운 기획 보고서가 마음에 듭니다.
Oh, really?
오, 진짜?
Totally. I think the department head will love it.
완전히. 부서장님이 좋아하실 것 같아요.
That's good to hear.
좋은 소식이네요.
♫ In the familiar meeting and parting ♫
♫ 익숙한 만남과 이별 속에서 ♫
♫ I hide my words ♫
♫ 나는 내 말을 숨긴다 ♫
Hold your positions. We will carry out our duties to the end.
위치를 유지하십시오. 우리는 끝까지 임무를 수행할 것입니다.
As if nothing happened to Yumi.
마치 유미에게는 아무 일도 일어나지 않았다는 듯이.
♫ will I be hurt? ♫
♫ 내가 상처받을까? ♫
♫ The past memories will come  ♫
♫ 지난 추억이 떠오를 거예요 ♫
♫  to me again with sadness ♫
♫ 다시 나에게 슬픔으로 ♫
It's been a while since I saw a clear sky.
오랜만에 맑은 하늘을 보았습니다.
♫ of the stories within me  ♫
♫ 내 안의 이야기 중 ♫
Oh! I can also see our village over there!
오! 저쪽에 우리 마을도 보이네요!
Guys, Yumi's back to normal.
여러분, 유미가 다시 정상으로 돌아왔습니다.
She's okay now. Let's go home!
이제 그녀는 괜찮아요. 집에 가자!
♫ In the season which passes  ♫
♫ 지나가는 계절에 ♫
♫ In the moment which stopped wordlessly ♫
♫ 말없이 멈춘 순간에 ♫
♫ which stopped wordlessly ♫
♫말 없이 멈춰 있던 ♫
♫ If it happens will you say to me? ♫
♫ 그런 일이 생기면 나한테 말해줄래? ♫
♫  "you did well" and "good job"? ♫
♫ "잘했어" 그리고 "수고했어"? ♫
I returned to my old self after six days.
나는 6일 만에 예전의 모습으로 돌아왔습니다.
They were six long days that felt like six months.
6개월처럼 긴 6일이었습니다.
It's a call. Who could it be?
전화야. 누구일까요?
It was 9:30 p.m. when we went to wash up.
오후 9시 30분이었다. 우리가 씻으러 갔을 때.
There aren't many people who would call at this hour.
이 시간에 전화하는 사람이 별로 없어요.
No way! Wung?
안 돼요! 웅?
It's not Wung.
웅이 아닙니다.
Wung could have changed his phone number.
Wung이 전화번호를 바꿨을 수도 있어요.
It may be the reason why he didn't pick up on that day.
그 사람이 그날 전화를 받지 않은 이유가 그것 때문일 수도 있습니다.
Come on! Hurry and answer. They'll hang up.
어서 해봐요! 서둘러 대답하세요. 전화를 끊을 거예요.
The touch screen won't work because of the soap.
비누 때문에 터치 스크린이 작동하지 않습니다.
Hello.
안녕하세요.
Si Yeon?
시연?
Did you change your number?
번호를 바꾸셨나요?
Oh yes, I'm doing well.
아, 네, 잘 지내요.
The moment you think it's over, you're tested again.
끝났다고 생각하는 순간 다시 시험을 당하게 된다.
You said Yumi was back to normal!
유미가 정상으로 돌아왔다고 하더군요!
Everyone hold on tight!
다들 꽉 붙잡으세요!
And another storm comes.
그리고 또 다른 폭풍이 옵니다.
At times like that, we restore Wung's number that we deleted
그럴 땐 삭제했던 웅 번호를 복원해
and look at his profile.
그리고 그 사람 프로필을 보세요.
He changed his profile. Gu Wung.
그는 프로필을 바꿨습니다. 구웅.
Wung deleted the couple photo six days after our breakup.
웡은 헤어진 지 6일 만에 커플 사진을 삭제했다.
Has he already moved on?
그는 이미 전진했는가?
♫ Nightfallin'  ♫
♫ 나이트폴링 ♫
♫ At the end of the sun setting ♫
♫ 해가 지는 마지막 순간에 ♫
♫ In me ♫
♫ 내 안에 ♫
♫ I feel you intensifying Sweet cologne Truth be told ♫
♫ 당신이 스위트 코롱을 강렬하게 하고 있는 게 느껴져요 진실을 말해주세요 ♫
♫ Sweet cologne ♫
♫ 달콤한 향수 ♫
♫ Truth be told ♫
♫ 진실을 말해주세요 ♫
♫ You and I, ♫
♫ 당신과 나, ♫
♫ we are walking to the same beat ♫
♫ 우리는 같은 박자에 맞춰 걷고 있어요 ♫
♫ Nightfallin'  ♫
♫ 나이트폴링 ♫
♫  Because you are within my two eyes ♫
♫ 당신은 내 두 눈 안에 있기 때문이죠 ♫
♫ I'm hiding the especially red cheeks,  ♫
♫ 유난히 붉은 볼을 숨기고 있어요 ♫
♫ Yes I know ♫
♫ 네, 알아요 ♫
If I look at Wung's friend Louis' social media...
웅 친구 루이의 SNS를 보면...
All-nighter. Feeling empty.
밤새도록. 공허한 느낌.
He has a friend named Ji Ni and I look at their friends.
그에게는 지니라는 친구가 있는데 나는 그 친구들을 바라본다.
If I go to Gi Yeong's account from the comments,
댓글에서 기영님 계정으로 들어가시면
I can see Wung after our break up.
이별 후에 웅을 볼 수 있어요.
He cut his hair.
그는 머리를 잘랐다.
It suits him.
그에게 어울린다.
♫ Wandering this time which is filled by you ♫
♫ 너로 가득찬 이 시간을 헤매며 ♫
♫  in this moment ♫
♫ 지금 이 순간 ♫
♫ even though it's a little constricted so I am out of breath ♫
♫ 조금 조여서 숨이 차는데도 ♫
♫ Will you lock us in this ecstasy? ♫
♫ 우리를 이 황홀경 속에 가두실 건가요? ♫
But, Eonni Yumi, are you really okay?
그런데 언니 유미 정말 괜찮아요?
What are you talking about?
무슨 얘기를 하는 건가요?
No one would know you went through a breakup if you didn't say anything.
아무 말도 하지 않으면 아무도 당신이 이별을 겪었다는 것을 알 수 없습니다.
Is that so?
그렇습니까?
I'm really not the type to show my emotions either.
저도 사실 감정을 드러내는 타입은 아니에요.
- You aren't? - I really don't show them. People tell me they don't know what I'm feeling.
- 그렇지 않나요? - 정말 안 보여요. 사람들은 내가 느끼는 감정을 모른다고 말합니다.
- Is that so? - But Eonni Yumi, how are you so cool?
- 그렇습니까? - 그런데 언니 유미 씨는 어쩜 그렇게 멋있나요?
I'm hungry.
배고파요.
Huh?
뭐?
- Pathetic, what is it? - Shhh.
- 한심해, 그게 뭐야? - 쉿.
Writer, can you write something for me, keeping it a secret from the other cells?
작가님, 다른 감방에는 비밀로 하여 저를 위해 글을 써주실 수 있나요?
Write something?
뭔가를 쓰시겠습니까?
Can you write something short that expresses Yumi being sad
유미가 슬퍼하는 모습을 짧게 써주실 수 있나요
after her breakup with Wung?
Wung과 헤어진 후?
I want to make it obvious somewhere.
어딘가에 분명히 밝히고 싶습니다.
Won't that look a bit pathetic?
좀 한심해 보이지 않나요?
That's why I'm asking you to make it short.
그렇기 때문에 짧게 해달라고 요청하는 것입니다.
Short? How short?
짧은? 얼마나 짧나요?
How short can you make it?
얼마나 짧게 할 수 있나요?
Status message
상태 메시지
Enter your status message.
상태 메시지를 입력하세요.
ㅜㅜ ("u u", which looks like tears falling from eyes and means "sad")
ㅜㅜ ("u u", 눈에서 눈물이 떨어지는 것처럼 보이며 "슬픔"을 의미함)
Kim Yumi ㅜㅜ
김유미 ㅜㅜ
Who is the person who seems to be everywhere but is nowhere?
어디에나 있는 것 같지만 어디에도 없는 사람은 누구일까요?
Answer.
답변.
A cool person.
멋진 사람.
Yumi♡ ㅜㅜ
유미♡ ㅜㅜ
Gu Wung .
구웅 .
Yumi♡ ㅜㅜ Gu Wung .
유미♡ ㅜㅜ 구웅 .
Episode 02 Cure
에피소드 02 치료
Daehan Noodles
대한국수
It is.
그것은.
What is this?
이게 뭔가요?
As soon as I entered the café, right when I thought it couldn't be that person ... it was that person!
카페에 들어가자마자 저 사람이 아닐 거라고 생각한 순간... 바로 저 사람이었습니다!
- That's crazy. - It was a total fail. It couldn't be worse than that.
- 말도 안 돼. - 완전 실패였어요. 이보다 더 나쁠 수는 없습니다.
- More than last time? - Yes.
- 지난번보다 더요? - 예.
- It can be even worse? - Worse do exist!
- 더 나쁠 수도 있나요? - 더 나쁜 것도 존재해요!
Yumi has an illness.
유미에게 질병이 있습니다.
I got it. Eonni, go home safely.
알겠어요. 언니야 집에 조심히 가세요.
- Okay. - Get home safely.
- 좋아요. - 집에 안전하게 도착하세요.
- See you next week. - Bye.
- 다음주에 뵙겠습니다. - 안녕.
Even though she's perfectly fine at work,
비록 그녀가 직장에서는 완벽하게 괜찮지만,
she can't breathe properly at night and is unable to sleep.
그녀는 밤에 제대로 숨을 쉴 수 없고 잠도 잘 수 없습니다.
I think she has a slight fever too.
내 생각엔 그 사람도 약간의 열이 있는 것 같아.
This is definitely a symptom of the Monday blues.
이것은 확실히 월요일 블루스의 증상입니다.
Today is Friday.
오늘은 금요일입니다.
This illness is the after-effect of a breakup.
이 병은 이별의 후유증이다.
The after-effect of breakup?
이별 후유증?
Breakup Aftereffect Symptoms can last for a few weeks up to several years.
이별 후유증 증상은 몇 주에서 몇 년 동안 지속될 수 있습니다.
It can go on for years?! What's the cure?
몇 년 동안 계속될 수 있나요?! 치료법은 무엇입니까?
There aren't any proven cures yet, but there are a variety of home remedies.
아직까지 입증된 치료법은 없지만 다양한 가정 요법이 있습니다.
You need medicine for the after-effects of a breakup.
이별 후유증에는 약이 필요하다.
What medicine? I heard there's no medicine.
무슨 약? 약이 없다고 들었습니다.
I will let you know the pharmacy I go to.
제가 다니는 약국을 알려드릴게요.
You can get the cure if you go here.
여기 가시면 치료 받으실 수 있어요.
♫ I also wouldn't know my heart ♫
♫ 나도 내 마음을 몰랐을 거야 ♫
It's close by, so go there right after you wake up.
근처에 있으니 일어나자마자 바로 가보세요.
♫ There's a me ♫
♫ 내가 있다 ♫
♫ I don't know ♫
♫ 모르겠어요 ♫
♫ Even if I walk slowly ♫
♫ 천천히 걸어도 ♫
♫ My heart is running far away there ♫
♫ 내 마음은 그곳으로 멀리 달려가고 있어요 ♫
♫ I don't know ♫
♫ 모르겠어요 ♫
♫ what's the matter with me ♫
♫ 나에게 무슨 문제가 있는 걸까요 ♫
♫ Even f I walk carefully  ♫
♫ 조심스럽게 걸어도 ♫
♫  my heart is far away there ♫
♫ 내 마음은 저기 멀리 있어요 ♫
It felt as if I was being played, but I decided to trust him this time.
마치 내가 놀리는 것 같은 느낌이 들었지만 이번에는 그를 믿기로 결정했습니다.
I was played by Hunger.
나는 Hunger에 의해 연기되었습니다.
There was no change in the symptoms even after eating.
식사 후에도 증상의 변화는 없었습니다.
It was tasty, though.
그래도 맛있었어요.
Buy her a pretty purse, that may make things better.
그녀에게 예쁜 지갑을 사주면 상황이 더 좋아질 수도 있습니다.
Do you think I'll fall for the same trick twice?
내가 같은 속임수에 두 번 빠질 것 같나요?
Shopping is a home remedy that's been passed down for generations.
쇼핑은 여러 세대에 걸쳐 전해 내려오는 가정 요법입니다.
Are you looking down on the effectiveness of shopping?
쇼핑의 효율성을 무시하고 계신가요?
This illness was caused by Wung's absence.
이 질병은 Wung의 부재로 인해 발생했습니다.
You need to fill that absence with something for her to get better!
그녀가 나아질 수 있도록 그 공백을 뭔가로 채워야 합니다!
Is that so?
그렇습니까?
I got played again. Money only got spent, but the symptom remains.
또 놀았어. 돈만 썼는데 증상이 남아있습니다.
It's because I can't feel anything.
아무것도 느낄 수 없기 때문이죠.
How about a late-night movie? Something very cheerful.
심야영화 어때요? 매우 쾌활한 것.
Hey, you scammers!
이봐, 사기꾼들아!
What are you going to do about Yumi? She's not getting any better.
유미를 어떻게 할 건가요? 그녀는 더 나아지지 않습니다.
All of you take responsibility! We only spent money!
모두 책임을 져라! 우리는 돈만 썼습니다!
I hope this isn't a terminal illness.
이것이 불치병이 아니길 바랍니다.
Yumi might die at this rate.
이대로라면 유미가 죽을 수도 있다.
What are you going to do!
당신은 무엇을 할 예정입니까!
Relax. I'll write you a prescription.
안심하다. 내가 처방전을 써줄게.
What prescription now?!
지금 무슨 처방전이요?!
Normal treatments won't do. We'll have to try something stronger.
일반적인 치료는 하지 않습니다. 우리는 더 강한 것을 시도해야 할 것입니다.
Beer?
맥주?
Her symptoms seem to be improving.
그녀의 증상은 호전되는 것 같습니다.
It really must be working.
정말 효과가 있을 것 같아요.
♪ Now, I won’t ever love again
♪ 이제 다시는 사랑하지 않을 거예요
Huh? What's going on?
뭐? 무슨 일이야?
♪ What I’m saying is that
♪ 내 말은
♪ because I can’t meet another one like you
♪너 같은 사람을 또 만날 수 없으니까
♪ I can’t love
♪ 사랑할 수가 없어
What is this? Medicine treatment precautions.
이게 뭔가요? 약물치료 주의사항.
Side effects can include singing sad songs?
부작용으로 슬픈 노래를 부르는 것도 포함될 수 있나요?
♪ I love you ♪
♪ 사랑해요 ♪
♪ Please forget
♪ 잊어주세요
♪ and erase me
♪ 그리고 나를 지워
♪ From now on, I won't love again
♪ 이제부터 다시는 사랑하지 않을 거예요
♪ From now on, I won't love again ♪
♪ 이제부터 다시는 사랑하지 않을 거예요 ♪
♪ You and me. Someone like me
♪ 너와 나. 나 같은 사람
♪ Because I can’t meet another person like you
♪ 너 같은 사람 또 만날 수 없으니까
♪ I can’t love anymore
♪ 더 이상 사랑할 수 없어
It's two in the morning now!
지금은 새벽 2시예요!
Yumi, lower your voice.
유미 씨, 목소리를 낮추세요.
♪ Like an idiot
♪ 바보처럼
♪ I won’t love - Wow! Crazy high notes!
♪ 사랑하지 않을 거야 - 와! 미친 높은 음표!
- Our Yumi sings well! - Yumi!
- 우리 유미가 노래를 잘해요! - 유미!
♪ Please forget
♪ 잊어주세요
♪ and erase me
♪ 그리고 나를 지워
Deep inside oneself
자신의 내면 깊은 곳
Guys, it's been a while!
여러분, 오랜만이에요!
We're in trouble! Inner Feelings came out because of the alcohol.
우리는 곤경에 빠졌습니다! 술 때문에 내면의 감정이 나왔다.
Guys, you know...
여러분, 아시죠...
What?
무엇?
I miss Wung.
웅이 그리워요.
Just today. It's just for today.
바로 오늘입니다. 오늘만이에요.
I'll just look for the last time today
오늘이 마지막으로 찾아볼게
and won't look anymore.
더 이상 보지 않을 것입니다.
It's a new picture.
새로운 사진이에요.
- Basketball after quite a while. - It's really exciting!
- 오랜만에 농구. - 정말 신난다!
They really do look excited.
정말 신나 보이는군요.
That can't be! Zoom in!
그럴 리가 없어! 확대!
There must be tears in his eyes.
그의 눈에는 눈물이 흐르고 있을 것입니다.
No, this is one hundred percent excitement.
아니요, 이것은 100% 흥분입니다.
This can't be.
이럴 수는 없습니다.
What is so exciting?
뭐가 그렇게 신나는 거야?
How can you be so excited?
어떻게 그렇게 흥분할 수 있나요?
I am stuck at home
집에 갇혀 있어요
being pitiful.
불쌍하다.
The treatment was unsuccessful.
치료가 실패했습니다.
We're leaving. Bye.
우리는 떠난다. 안녕.
Aren't you going home?
집에 안 갈 거야?
I need to organize some things. You go ahead.
몇 가지를 정리해야 해요. 계속하세요.
I am not going either.
나도 가지 않을 거야.
- What? - I have to work overtime.
- 무엇? - 초과근무를 해야 해요.
I see.
알겠어요.
Call me if you're hungry, I have to eat dinner as well.
배고프면 전화해, 나도 저녁 먹어야 해.
Sure.
확신하는.
She's not organizing but just wasting time.
그녀는 정리를 하지 않고 단지 시간만 낭비할 뿐입니다.
Why? Because there's nothing to do at home anyway.
왜? 어차피 집에서는 할 일이 없으니까.
But Wung must be out having fun.
하지만 Wung은 즐겁게 놀고 있을 것 같아요.
- It's a fire! - The village is on fire again!
- 불이에요! - 마을에 또 불이 붙었어요!
Please stop thinking about Wung.
Wung에 대해 생각하지 마십시오.
We need to divert Yumi's attention to something else.
유미의 관심을 다른 데로 돌려야 합니다.
Reason, I have found the cure.
이유야, 치료법을 찾았어.
What?
무엇?
This is the best home remedy with the highest cure rate for the after-effects of a breakup!
이별후유증 치료율이 가장 높은 최고의 가정요법!
To throw everything that is related to Wung today,
오늘은 Wung과 관련된 모든 것을 던지기 위해
that she wasn't able to throw away before.
예전에는 버리지 못했던 것.
Ba Bi, I'm hungry. Let's eat and then continue.
바비, 배고파요. 먹고 계속하자.
Shall we? Hold on, I'll go and ask if Assistant Manager Yumi also wants to come.
우리 할까요? 잠깐만요, 유미 대리도 올 의향이 있는지 제가 가서 물어보겠습니다.
Sure.
확신하는.
Assistant Manager Yumi, will you have dinner—
유미 대리 저녁 드실래요—
Yes. If I can't let go of Wung now
예. 지금 웅을 놓을 수 없다면
until when, will I have no life?
언제까지 나에게 생명이 없겠는가?
Today I will throw away all the things that I have which are related to Wung.
오늘은 제가 가지고 있는 웅과 관련된 모든 것을 버리겠습니다.
The first item is the poster of the game that Wung was developing.
첫 번째 아이템은 Wung이 개발하고 있던 게임의 포스터입니다.
How am I supposed to throw this away? It's really big.
이걸 어떻게 버려야 하지? 정말 크다.
You should tear it up and throw it away.
찢어서 버려야 합니다.
But it's a poster of the game Wung made.
그런데 웅이 만든 게임 포스터네요.
It's something very meaningful to Wung.
이는 Wung에게 매우 의미 있는 일입니다.
Yeah, tear it up.
응, 찢어버려
Yumi!
유미!
Can you get up for a sec?
잠깐 일어나 주시겠어요?
The poster is too far to the left in relation to the bed.
포스터가 침대에 비해 너무 왼쪽에 있습니다.
What?
무엇?
No, no, you cannot get lost in your memories.
아니, 아니, 추억 속에서 길을 잃을 수는 없습니다.
We were so happy back then.
그때 우리는 너무 행복했어요.
Stop being so sentimental!
너무 감상적이지 마세요!
What's wrong with the poster? We broke up!
포스터에 무슨 문제가 있나요? 우리 헤어졌어!
We don't know if Wung will come back later to get it.
Wung이 나중에 다시 와서 그것을 얻을지 여부는 알 수 없습니다.
He said they didn't make that many posters.
포스터를 그렇게 많이 만들지는 않았다고 하더군요.
Okay, all right. We'll leave the poster for now.
알았어, 알았어. 지금은 포스터를 남겨 두겠습니다.
We'll keep this and throw away the rest.
우리는 이것을 유지하고 나머지는 버릴 것입니다.
Next, our couple T-shirt.  [Yummy Cracker]
다음은 우리 커플 티셔츠에요.  [맛있는 크래커]
We bought it to wear when we work out.
운동할 때 입으려고 샀어요.
The blue one is yours.
파란색은 당신 것입니다.
Let's see.
어디 보자.
- It's nice. - Isn't it pretty?
- 좋네요. - 예쁘지 않나요?
- Try it on. - Now?
- 한번 입어보세요. - 지금?
All right, that's enough. Let's burn it and throw it away.
알았어, 그거면 충분해. 태워서 버리자.
Hold on! That shirt fits perfectly and the fabric is so nice
기다리다! 그 셔츠는 딱 맞고 옷감도 너무 좋아요
that it's perfect to lounge in. - We have plenty to lounge in.
휴식을 취하기에 완벽하다는 것입니다. - 쉴 곳이 많아요.
It's the best. It doesn't even say it's a couple t-shirt. So why not?
최고입니다. 커플티셔츠라고도 안 나오네요. 그렇다면 왜 안되나요?
That's right, the fabric is really nice. Why would I throw it out?
그렇죠, 원단이 정말 좋아요. 내가 왜 그것을 버리겠습니까?
I can use it as a rag.
걸레로 사용할 수 있어요.
There's no mercy from now on. Throw everything away. Okay, the keyboard.
이제부터 자비는 없습니다. 모든 것을 버리십시오. 좋아, 키보드야.
No! I'm against that.
아니요! 나는 그것에 반대합니다.
What now? Why?
지금은 무엇입니까? 왜?
My fingers are already used to that keyboard, so it's uncomfortable if it's not that one.
내 손가락은 이미 그 키보드에 익숙해져 있어서, 그 키보드가 아니면 불편하다.
You can get used to another one!
다른 것에 익숙해 질 수 있습니다!
If I change the keyboard and get a slump, are you going to take responsibility?
키보드를 바꿔서 슬럼프가 오면 책임지실 건가요?
What kind of nonsense is that? Just throw it away!
그게 무슨 말도 안되는 소리입니까? 그냥 버려!
Keyboard
키보드
What is this keyboard?
이 키보드는 뭔가요?
It's your first day at the marketing department tomorrow.
내일은 마케팅 부서에서의 첫날입니다.
It's a present. That's the best mechanical keyboard there is.
선물이에요. 현존하는 최고의 기계식 키보드입니다.
Famous writers all use that. I want you to write good things.
유명한 작가들은 모두 그것을 사용합니다. 좋은 글 써주셨으면 좋겠습니다.
I'll keep it until I get used to a new keyboard.
새 키보드에 익숙해질 때까지 보관하겠습니다.
Next is the necklace she got for her birthday.
다음은 생일 선물로 받은 목걸이입니다.
Let's really throw this away. This will be a cure if we throw it away.
이건 정말 버리자. 버리면 치료제가 될 것입니다.
Are you all crazy?
다들 미쳤어?
You kept the paper poster, fabric, and everything else,
당신은 종이 포스터, 천, 기타 모든 것을 보관했습니다.
so why would you throw away a gold necklace?!
그런데 왜 금목걸이를 버리시겠습니까?!
You could sell it! If you're going to throw it away, then throw everything away!
당신은 그것을 팔 수 있습니다! 버릴 거면 다 버려라!
Why would you only throw away the gold?!
왜 금만 버리겠습니까?!
Start digging and see if you can find gold so easily.
땅을 파기 시작해서 금을 그렇게 쉽게 찾을 수 있는지 알아보세요.
Okay, okay. I'll put the necklace on hold for now.
알았어, 알았어. 목걸이는 일단 보류하겠습니다.
What's the next item? The next item, what is it?
다음 항목은 무엇입니까? 다음 항목은 무엇입니까?
Ribbit
개빗
It's a frog.
개구리입니다.
Do you remember? The frog that saved us.
기억하시나요? 우리를 구해준 개구리.
Wung's frog.
웅의 개구리.
Hi, Yumi's love cell.
안녕하세요 유미의 사랑세포입니다.
- Who are you? - I'm Wung's love cell.
- 누구세요? - 저는 웅의 사랑세포입니다.
What?
무엇?
it's raining.
비가 온다.
How did it go? Did my prescription work?
어떻게 됐나요? 내 처방전이 효과가 있었나요?
Its effectiveness was crap. The symptoms got worse.
그 효율성은 쓰레기였습니다. 증상은 더욱 심해졌습니다.
Can't you see it's raining?
비오는거 안보여?
Hello?
안녕하세요?
Assistant Manager Yumi, when did you leave? I saw you were gone.
유미 대리님은 언제 퇴사하셨나요? 나는 당신이 사라진 것을 보았습니다.
Oh, yes. I came home because I had something to do.
아, 그렇죠. 할 일이 있어서 집에 왔어요.
Then, I'll come by your place in a bit. Can you come out for a second? I'm leaving now.
그럼 조금 있다가 네 집으로 갈게. 잠깐 나와주실 수 있나요? 나는 지금 떠난다.
What? Is there something wrong?
무엇? 뭔가 문제가 있나요?
The proposal revision just came out. I think it'd be good if you check it out too.
제안 개정안이 방금 나왔습니다. 여러분들도 확인해보시면 좋을 것 같아요.
I only have a hard copy.
저는 하드 카피만 갖고 있어요.
I see. Sounds good to me.
알겠어요. 나에게는 좋은 것 같습니다.
- Call me when you arrive. - I will.
- 도착하면 전화하세요. - 그럴게요.
Where is he?
그는 어디에 있나요?
Assistant Manager Yu Ba Bi Hang in there.
유바비 대리 조금만 참으세요.
I'll be just a moment, sir.
잠시만 기다리겠습니다.
- Did you wait long? - No.
- 오래 기다리셨나요? - 아니요.
I'm sorry there was some traffic up here.
여기 교통 정체가 있어서 미안해요.
Here you go.
여기요.
It's a secret that I gave it to you. Take a look at it and return it in secret, please.
내가 준 건 비밀이야. 꼭 보시고 비밀리에 돌려주세요.
Sure, thank you.
물론이죠. 감사합니다.
- I'll get going then. - I'll see you tomorrow.
- 그럼 바로 갈게요. - 내일 봐요.
- You're okay, right? - Excuse me?
- 괜찮아요? - 실례합니다?
Hang in there.
조금만 참으세요.
We can go, sir.
우리는 갈 수 있습니다.
Time is the only cure for the after-effect of a breakup.
이별 후유증에 대한 유일한 치료법은 시간이다.
However, one phrase can be a great treatment.
하지만 문구 하나가 훌륭한 치료법이 될 수 있습니다.
Assistant Manager Yu Ba Bi Hang in there.
유바비 대리 조금만 참으세요.
Let's go!
갑시다!
Episode 03: Yu Ba Bi Club
03회: 유바비클럽
- Even though it's daytime, I'm not sweating even a bit today, right? - Yes.
- 낮인데도 오늘은 땀이 조금도 나지 않죠? - 예.
Fall must already be here.
벌써 가을이 와있나봐요.
It's fall already?
벌써 가을이네?
Time really flies by.
시간이 정말 빨리 지나갑니다.
Come with me next time, it's on me.
다음에는 나랑 같이 가세요. 그건 나 몫이에요.
Isn't that Ruby?
루비 아닌가요?
Why do you always pay?
왜 항상 돈을 내나요?
- Thank you for the meal. - It's no problem. It's on me again the next time.
- 식사해주셔서 감사합니다. - 문제없어요. 다음번에도 나한테 달려있네
- That's Assistant Manager Yu Ba Bi from your department, right? - Yes.
- 귀 부서 유바비 대리 맞죠? - 예.
How is she friends with people from other departments?
그녀는 다른 부서 사람들과 어떻게 친구가 되나요?
- It's impressive. - I'll see you later.
- 인상적이네요. - 나중에 봐요.
Bye!
안녕!
Ruby! Lee Ruby!
루비! 리루비!
Hi! I was going to go get coffee.
안녕! 커피 마시러 가려고 했는데
Eonni, what kind of person is Yu Ba Bi?
언니, 유바비는 어떤 사람이에요?
What? Yu Ba Bi?
무엇? 유바비?
Yes, Assistant Manager Yu Ba Bi. What kind of person is he?
네, 유바비 대리님. 그는 어떤 사람인가요?
- You know him too, though. - You're closer to him than me.
- 하지만 당신도 그 사람을 알아요. - 당신은 나보다 그 사람과 더 가깝습니다.
You're both older, in the same department, and live in the same neighborhood.
당신은 둘 다 나이가 많고, 같은 부서에 있고, 같은 동네에 살고 있습니다.
But why are you suddenly asking?
그런데 갑자기 왜 묻는 겁니까?
'Cause I'm curious.
궁금해서요.
- Why are you curious? - Right.
- 왜 궁금해요? - 오른쪽.
That's a secret!
그건 비밀이에요!
Give me some information on Yu Ba Bi.
유바비에 대한 정보를 알려주세요.
- Thank you. - She's always like that.
- 감사합니다. - 그녀는 항상 그런 식이에요.
I think I know why she's curious. That girl...
나는 그녀가 왜 궁금해하는지 알 것 같아요. 그 여자...
Guys, what kind of person is Yu Ba Bi?
여러분, 유바비는 어떤 사람인가요?
If anyone knows, can you raise your hand? I need information on Yu Ba Bi.
아시는 분 계시다면 손을 들어주실 수 있나요? 유바비에 대한 정보가 필요해요.
Is there really not one cell that knows anything about Yu Ba Bi?
정말 유바비에 대해 아는 세포가 하나도 없는 걸까요?
- How about going to the club area to check? - Go to check the club area?
- 클럽 구역에 가서 확인해 보는 건 어때요? - 클럽 지역을 확인하러 가시나요?
Because Yu Ba Bi is a good person, there may even be a Yu Ba Bi club.
유바비가 좋은 사람이라 유바비 동호회도 있을 수도 있다.
Even if Yumi shows only a little interest about something, a club will be created. Yumi Club Area
유미가 어떤 일에 조금이라도 관심을 보이더라도 동아리가 만들어지겠죠. 유미 클럽 구역
It's really good. It's all really good.
정말 좋아요. 모두 정말 좋습니다.
Is it good?
좋은가요?
It's really good.
정말 좋아요.
What makes it taste like this?
왜 이런 맛이 나는 걸까요?
It's really good, right?
정말 좋은데요, 그렇죠?
I like stone crab more than blue crab.
저는 꽃게보다 돌게를 더 좋아해요.
Stone crab?
돌게?
This is stone crab. This place is known for it.
돌게 입니다. 이곳은 유명합니다.
Stone crab? This is stone crab?
돌게? 이게 돌게인가요?
What's the difference between the two?
둘 사이의 차이점은 무엇입니까?
Seaside Village Marinated Crab It's cheap and delicious.
해변마을 양념게 저렴하고 맛있습니다.
Sign up for the club!
클럽에 가입하세요!
The best stone crab club. - Take a look.
최고의 돌게 클럽. - 한번 보세요.
A new stone crab club has formed.
새로운 돌게 동호회가 결성되었습니다.
Hurry and sign up.
서둘러서 가입하세요.
Reason, will you join the stone crab club?
이유야, 돌게 동호회에 가입할래?
We research everything about stone crabs.
돌게에 관한 모든 것을 연구합니다.
I will explain the difference between a stone crab and a blue crab.
돌게와 꽃게의 차이점을 설명하겠습니다.
Hey, where are you going?
이봐, 어디 가는 거야?
You can sign there.
거기에 서명하시면 됩니다.
Here? Sign here?
여기? 여기에 서명하시겠습니까?
Everyone, join the puppy club.
여러분, 강아지 클럽에 가입하세요.
Cute cute puppies!
귀엽고 귀여운 강아지들!
Did Yumi still have this many interests?
유미가 아직도 이렇게 관심이 많았나요?
If Yumi loses interest,
유미가 흥미를 잃으면
the club may close.
클럽이 문을 닫을 수도 있습니다.
Let's call Min Ho from SHINee, Oppa.
샤이니 민호를 오빠라고 불러요.
Join the Min Ho club. Choi Min Ho
민호클럽에 가입하세요. 최민호
Charismatic Min Ho!
카리스마 민호!
The Dong Gook Oppa club of 20 years is dying!
20년 동국오빠 동아리가 죽어갑니다!
Please join!
참여해주세요!
When Yumi was 20, there were so many clubs.
유미가 20살이었을 때는 동아리가 정말 많았어요.
But there's still a lot left.
하지만 아직 많이 남았습니다.
He's so sexy. I want Gong Yoo.
그는 너무 섹시해요. 나는 공유를 원한다.
What are you doing here?
여기서 뭐하는거야?
Naughty, you!
장난 꾸러기, 당신!
Gong Yoo Club
공유클럽
Naughty, you punk. You haven't been around lately and now...
버릇없어, 이 새끼야. 최근에 안 오셨는데 지금은...
If you aren't going to join, can you get lost?
참여하지 않으면 길을 잃을 수 있나요?
Are there any cells here that know Yu Ba Bi well?
여기 유바비를 잘 아는 세포가 있나요?
Yu Ba Bi?
유바비?
I need some information about Yu Ba Bi.
유바비에 대한 정보가 필요해요.
You can ask about that over there.
그건 거기에 물어보시면 됩니다.
Ba Bi Club.
바비클럽.
What's this?
이건 뭐죠?
There was really a Yu Ba Bi Club?
정말 유바비클럽이 있었나요?
Excuse me.
실례합니다.
B A B I. Ba Bi.
B A B I. 바비.
- Is this the Yu Ba Bi club– - Nice.
- 여기가 유바비 동호회인가요? - 좋아요.
B I–
B I–
Hey! Yumi's Guard, why are you here?
여기요! 유미의 경비병, 당신은 왜 여기에 있습니까?
Don't misunderstand. I just arrived here to destroy the club.
오해하지 마세요. 나는 클럽을 파괴하기 위해 여기에 도착했습니다.
President, you came in early today again.
대통령님, 오늘도 일찍 오셨습니다.
You're the president?!
당신이 대통령인가요?!
I can't believe it. You were the one who opposed Yu Ba Bi the most.
믿을 수가 없어요. 유바비를 가장 반대한 사람은 당신이었습니다.
Are you here to join too?
당신도 합류하러 왔나요?
Do I look crazy?
내가 미친 것처럼 보이나요?
Give me some information about Yu Ba Bi. Ruby wants to know.
유바비에 대한 정보를 알려주세요. 루비는 알고 싶어합니다.
Why Ruby?
왜 루비인가?
Will you just answer my question?
내 질문에 그냥 대답해줄래?
Yu Ba Bi likes to read novels.
유바비는 소설 읽는 걸 좋아해요.
I think he reads whenever he has free time.
내 생각에 그 사람은 시간이 날 때마다 책을 읽는 것 같아요.
He buys new books and reads them right away.
그는 새 책을 사서 바로 읽습니다.
What genre does he like?
그는 어떤 장르를 좋아하나요?
Genre?
장르?
I don't know what genre but he likes books.
어떤 장르인지는 모르겠지만 책을 좋아해요.
What does it say?
그것은 무엇을 말합니까?
I was wondering what you were reading.
나는 당신이 무엇을 읽고 있는지 궁금했습니다.
Have you read this? It's a bestseller in fiction these days.
이것을 읽어 보셨나요? 요즘 소설계 베스트셀러죠.
No, not yet, but I heard it was interesting.
아니요, 아직은 아니지만 흥미롭다고 들었습니다.
I have barely read any books lately.
나는 최근에 책을 거의 읽지 않았다.
It's really interesting. I also recommend it.
정말 흥미롭습니다. 나는 또한 그것을 추천한다.
Really? I'll have to write it down.
정말? 적어야 겠습니다.
I finished reading it.
나는 그것을 다 읽었다.
What?
무엇?
Read it and return it.
읽어보시고 돌려주세요.
Daehan Noodles making the world more delicious. 'A Perfect Day'
세상을 더 맛있게 만드는 대한면. '완벽한 하루'
Thank you.
감사합니다.
Ba Bi Club
바비 클럽
President, why are you erasing that?
대통령님, 그걸 왜 지우시나요?
I don't feel comfortable.
기분이 좋지 않아요.
Now that Reason knows, I think he will interfere with our activities.
이제 이성이 알았으니 우리 활동을 방해할 것 같아요.
We need to change it to a private club.
비공개 클럽으로 바꿔야 해요.
Then we're not even going to promote it?
그럼 우리는 홍보도 안 할 건가요?
We don't need to promote because we're a private élite club.
우리는 민간 엘리트 클럽이기 때문에 홍보할 필요가 없습니다.
Why? Why do we need to be private?
왜? 왜 우리는 비공개여야 합니까?
Ba Bi is interested in Ruby, you idiot.
바비는 루비에게 관심이 있다, 멍청아.
And Yumi hasn't taken care of Wung's things.
그리고 Yumi는 Wung의 물건을 돌보지 않았습니다.
There's no need for misunderstandings. We can just have fun among ourselves.
오해할 필요가 없습니다. 우리끼리만 재미있게 놀 수 있어요.
It's really interesting.
정말 흥미롭습니다.
I guess Assistant Manager Yu also likes sweet stories.
유 대리도 달달한 이야기를 좋아하는 것 같아요.
That guy.
그 사람.
He has a good eye for novels.
그는 소설에 대한 안목이 좋다.
Writer?
작가?
This is the Yu Ba Bi club, right?
여기 유바비 동호회 맞죠?
No.
아니요.
Come on, I heard all the rumors. I want to join this club.
어서, 소문은 다 들었어. 나는 이 클럽에 가입하고 싶다.
I like his taste in books. I think if he recommended other books, I would like it.
나는 그의 책 취향을 좋아한다. 그 분이 다른 책도 추천해 주시면 좋을 것 같아요.
I'm sorry but we are a private club–
죄송하지만 저희는 비공개 클럽입니다.
I'll be quiet!
나는 조용히 할 것이다!
I won't make it obvious. It's been so long since I met a guy who likes novels.
나는 그것을 명백하게 밝히지 않을 것이다. 소설 좋아하는 남자를 만난 건 정말 오랜만이다.
This is like meeting a national treasure! Please!
국보를 만난 기분이에요! 제발!
My goodness.
이럴 수가.
It's interesting.
흥미롭다.
I enjoyed the book.
나는 책을 즐겼다.
Did you finish reading it already?
벌써 다 읽으셨나요?
Yes. It was so interesting I stayed up all night.
예. 너무 흥미로워서 밤새도록 잤어요.
- It's interesting, right? - It really is.
- 흥미롭죠? - 정말이에요.
I knew you would like it.
나는 당신이 그것을 좋아할 것이라는 것을 알았습니다.
Should I recommend you some similar ones?
비슷한 것을 추천해야 할까요?
Really?
정말?
It's been a while since I read an interesting book, so I'm motivated to read.
오랜만에 재미있는 책을 읽어서 읽고 싶은 의욕이 생겼습니다.
I have a lot. Don't buy, borrow them from me instead. I'll lend them to you.
나는 많이 가지고 있습니다. 사지 말고 대신 나한테 빌려주세요. 내가 빌려줄게.
Ba Bi Club Members: 4
바비클럽 회원 수: 4
Stingy?
적은?
As of today, I decided to join the Yu Ba Bi club.
저는 오늘부로 유바비 동호회에 가입하기로 결정했습니다.
A man who lends books for free is the best.
책을 무료로 빌려주는 남자가 최고다.
We don't accept members. It's a private club.
우리는 회원을 받아들이지 않습니다. 프라이빗 클럽이에요.
How much do you want? Huh?
얼마를 원하시나요? 뭐?
Ba Bi Club
바비 클럽
What are you listening to?
무엇을 듣고 있나요?
What?
무엇?
You look like you're having fun.
당신은 즐거운 시간을 보내고 있는 것 같습니다.
Oh, this?
아, 이거요?
Can I listen to it too?
나도 들어봐도 될까?
Yes, of course.
물론이죠.
Sounds good. This must be ska music.
좋은 것 같아요. 이건 스카 음악이겠군요.
Yes.
예.
You must like electrifying music.
신나는 음악을 좋아하시나 봐요.
Ba Bi Club Members: 5
바비 클럽 회원 수: 5
To be honest, I'm tone-deaf. I don't know much about music.
솔직히 말해서 저는 음치입니다. 나는 음악에 대해 잘 모른다.
But in ska music, I really like the sound of 'ing.'
그런데 스카 음악에서는 'ing' 소리를 정말 좋아해요.
I can't explain it well but it's...
잘 설명할 수는 없지만...
This is what you're talking about, the 'ing' sound.
이것이 바로 'ing' 소리에 대해 말하는 것입니다.
Yes, that's right. "Ing".
네, 맞습니다. "잉".
- The "ing" sound. - Yes.
- "ing"소리. - 예.
I think it sounds good. Ba Bi Club Members: 8
제 생각엔 좋은 것 같아요. 바비 클럽 회원 수: 8
Oh, right now. ♫ –ing ♫
아, 지금 당장요. ♫ –ing ♫
What the–
뭐야-
I want to join this club. I just got the feeling.
나는 이 클럽에 가입하고 싶다. 방금 느낌이 들었습니다.
You can't! This is now a private club.
당신은 할 수 없습니다! 이것은 이제 개인 클럽입니다.
Quiet cells quietly being fans.
조용한 세포들이 조용히 팬이 되고 있습니다.
You guys.
여러분.
Let's go in!
들어가자!
I'll recommend a ska band that I like.
제가 좋아하는 스카밴드를 추천해드릴게요.
This is perfect for turning up the volume and doing chores at home.
볼륨을 높이고 집에서 집안일을 하는 데 적합합니다.
My Cotton Candy - Kingston Rudieska
내 솜사탕 - 킹스턴 루디스카
Assistant Manager Ba Bi likes ska music.
바비 대리는 스카 음악을 좋아해요.
Ska? What's ska?
스카? 스카는요?
Look it up. It's a thing.
찾아보세요. 그것은 일이다.
♫ A day that welcomes me with a smile ♫
♫ 미소로 나를 반기는 하루 ♫
♫ Leisurely driving by a street parade ♫
♫ 거리 퍼레이드를 따라 여유롭게 운전 중 ♫
♫ The footsteps that I walked became a melody ♫
♫ 내가 걸어온 발걸음은 멜로디가 되었어 ♫
Ba Bi Club Members: 21 ♫ We're making our own song ♫
바비클럽 회원 수: 21 ♫ 우리는 우리만의 노래를 만들고 있어요 ♫
Assistant Manager Yumi.
유미 대리.
Are you busy?
바쁘세요?
I need to deliver documents to the team meeting.
팀 회의에 문서를 전달해야 해요.
Then I'll talk fast. You know Kingston Rudieska, right?
그럼 빨리 얘기할게요. 킹스턴 루디스카를 아시죠?
- The ska band you recommended last time, right? - Yes.
- 저번에 추천해주신 스카밴드죠? - 예.
Yes, I know them. I liked them a lot. I listen to them every day.
예, 저는 그들을 알고 있습니다. 나는 그들을 많이 좋아했습니다. 나는 매일 그 말을 듣습니다.
That band is busking in Ilsan.
그 밴드가 일산에서 버스킹을 하고 있어요.
There was an announcement just now.
방금 공지가 떴네요.
Really? Sounds fun.
정말? 재미있을 것 같네요.
Do you want to go with me?
나와 함께 갈래?
It's a chance to listen to them live.
라이브로 들을 수 있는 기회입니다.
When is it?
언제입니까?
It's tonight.
오늘 밤이에요.
Yumi's Club Zone
유미의 클럽 존
I definitely thought I heard something around here.
분명 이 근처에서 무슨 말을 들은 것 같았어요.
I heard someone saying Yu Ba Bi to fall for us.
누군가 유바비가 우리한테 반하라고 말하는 걸 들었어요.
I probably misheard.
아마 내가 잘못 들었나 보다.
Ba Bi is interested in Ruby. Why would he be interested in Yumi?
바비는 루비에게 관심이 있어요. 그가 유미에게 관심을 갖는 이유는 무엇일까?
Ba Bi Club
바비 클럽
- Today? - Yes.
- 오늘? - 예.
Do you have plans tonight?
오늘 밤에 계획 있어요?
No, I don't.
아니요, 그렇지 않습니다.
Then come with me.
그럼 나와 함께 가세요.
Ba Bi Club Number of Members: 52
바비클럽 회원 수: 52
What's happening?
무슨 일이야?
Our Ba Bi. Ba Bi
우리 바비. 바비
Wh-wh-what are you guys doing?
뭐-뭐-뭐하는거야?
Why are you all crowded together like that?
왜 이렇게 다 모여있나요?
Come with me.
나와 함께 가자.
I don't know if I can...
할 수 있을지 모르겠어요...
You can.
당신은 할 수 있습니다.
Firmly cover it up. A terrible accident could happen.
단단히 덮어주세요. 끔찍한 사고가 일어날 수도 있습니다.
These guys are out of their minds anyway.
어쨌든 이 놈들은 정신이 나갔네요.
How could they make a club?
어떻게 클럽을 만들 수 있었나요?
They caused a problem when I let my guard down.
내가 방심했을 때 그들은 문제를 일으켰습니다.
Our Ba Bi.
우리 바비.
Marketing Department
마케팅부
What's going on?
무슨 일이야?
Testing. Can you hear me?
테스트. 내 말 들려요?
It's the president of the "Yu Ba Bi Club."
'유바비클럽' 회장입니다.
Calling all the secret members of the Yu Ba Bi Club.
유바비클럽의 비밀멤버들을 모두 불러냅니다.
Put on your uniforms and come to the village square.
교복을 입고 마을 광장으로 오세요.
From this moment on,
지금부터
the Yu Ba Bi club will
유바비 클럽은
be open to the public!
대중에게 공개하세요!
Kingston Rudieska Busking
킹스턴 루디스카 버스킹
They're too hard on us.
그들은 우리에게 너무 가혹합니다.
Are you guys crazy? Have you gone crazy?
너희들 미쳤어? 미쳤어?
Why did we come here with him?
우리는 왜 그 사람과 함께 여기에 왔습니까?
Hey! Get it together!
여기요! 함께하세요!
Is Yu Ba Bi a celebrity? Is he an idol?
유바비가 연예인인가요? 그는 아이돌인가요?
Yu Ba Bi is not someone to be a fan of!
유바비는 팬이 될 사람이 아니다!
Move.
이동하다.
So what are you guys going to do?
그럼 너희들은 무엇을 할 건가요?
Are you guys thinking of dating Yu Ba Bi?
혹시 유바비랑 사귈 생각 있으신가요?
Yu Ba Bi is kind to everyone.
유바비는 누구에게나 친절해요.
And he's interested in Ruby.
그리고 그는 Ruby에 관심이 있습니다.
You guys don't know? You guys know that.
여러분, 모르시나요? 여러분은 그것을 알고 있습니다.
Are you saying we're going to start having a crush again?
우리가 다시 짝사랑을 시작한다는 말인가요?
Are we going to be embarrassed like we were with Wu Gi?!
우리도 우기처럼 쑥스러워할 건가요?!
Just think of it as coming to listen to music.
그냥 음악 들으러 왔다고 생각하시면 됩니다.
In case you feel uncomfortable.
불편함을 느끼신다면.
No, I don't.
아니요, 그렇지 않습니다.
It's okay, I'm fine. I'm not cold.
괜찮아, 난 괜찮아 나는 춥지 않다.
It's starting.
시작됩니다.
Everyone! It's good to see you! We are Kingston Rudieska!
모든 사람! 만나서 반가워요! 우리는 킹스턴 루디스카입니다!
Thank you for so many of you coming here! We'll start!
많은 분들이 와주셔서 감사합니다! 시작하겠습니다!
Guys! First, everyone, disperse.
얘들아! 우선 다들 해산하세요.
Disperse, then go home and calm–
해산하고 집에 가서 진정하세요–
♫ A day that welcomes me with a smile ♫
♫ 미소로 나를 반기는 하루 ♫
♫ Leisurely driving by a street parade ♫
♫ 거리 퍼레이드를 따라 여유롭게 운전 중 ♫
♫ My footsteps became a melody ♫
♫ 내 발걸음은 멜로디가 되었어 ♫
Oh yeah!
아 그래!
Yay!
이야!
Let's go Yu Ba Bi!
가자 유바비!
Isn't this great?
정말 좋지 않나요?
♫ Traveling towards that wide ocean ♫
♫ 저 넓은 바다를 향해 여행 중 ♫
♫ Everyday, everynight I'll be there for you ♫
♫ 매일, 매일 밤 내가 당신 곁에 있을게요 ♫
♫ You raise me up I'm in love with you ♫
♫ 당신이 나를 일으켜 주었어요 난 당신을 사랑해요 ♫
The trombone!
트롬본!
Do you want ice cream?
아이스크림 먹을래?
Sounds good.
좋은 것 같아요.
Hello, what can I get you?
안녕하세요, 무엇을 드릴까요?
I'll have the original.
원본은 제가 갖겠습니다.
Here you go. Enjoy.
여기요. 즐기다.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
It must be good. I should get that too.
그것은 좋은 것임에 틀림없다. 나도 받아야겠다.
- Can I have the same? - Sure.
- 나도 똑같이 먹어도 될까요? - 확신하는.
I didn't say anything yet, though.
그런데 아직 아무 말도 안 했어요.
Even if you don't, it's written all over your face.
그렇지 않아도 얼굴에 다 써있습니다.
- It is? - Yes.
- 그것은? - 예.
That's not true.
그것은 사실이 아닙니다.
- I have a very good poker face– - No, you don't.
- 나는 아주 좋은 포커페이스를 가지고 있다. - 아니, 그렇지 않아요.
I don't?
나는 아니에요?
Not at all.
별말씀을요.
Was it the first time when I tried to tell you I found your umbrella in the park?
내가 공원에서 우산을 찾았다고 말하려던 게 처음이었나요?
Excuse me.
실례합니다.
- Me? - Yes.
- 나? - 예.
By chance, are you Kim Yumi?
혹시 김유미이신가요?
How do you know my name?
내 이름을 어떻게 아세요?
You're Assistant Manager Kim Yumi, right?
김유미 대리 맞죠?
The word "cautious" was written all over your face.
당신의 얼굴에는 '조심'이라는 단어가 적혀 있었습니다.
Really?
정말?
So I thought you were a very timid person but...
그래서 굉장히 소심한 사람인 줄 알았는데...
Did you lose your umbrella?
우산을 잃어버렸나요?
- Excuse me? - It has a fried egg on it.
- 실례합니다? - 계란 후라이가 들어있어요.
That's mine! The fried egg. Yes, that's mine.
그건 내 꺼야! 튀긴 계란입니다. 네, 그건 내 거예요.
But right away I was surprised.
그러나 나는 곧바로 놀랐다.
I realized you were a very bright person.
나는 당신이 매우 밝은 사람이라는 것을 깨달았습니다.
I guess I do show it.
보여주고 있는 것 같아요.
- Your face shows what you like and don't like right away. - Does it?
- 당신의 얼굴은 당신이 좋아하는 것과 싫어하는 것을 바로 보여줍니다. - 그렇죠?
And it shows when you are flustered.
그리고 그것은 당신이 당황할 때를 보여줍니다.
It does?
그렇죠?
You have the ring, right?
반지 갖고 계시죠?
What?
무엇?
I guess you figured it out then.
그때 알아낸 것 같아요.
And one can tell what you are curious about.
그리고 당신이 궁금해하는 것이 무엇인지 알 수 있습니다.
Oh, really?
오, 진짜?
If I find someone nice, I plan on hanging out with them.
좋은 사람을 찾으면 그 사람과 어울릴 생각이에요.
Yes.
예.
Then, by chance, are you interested in a blind–
그럼 혹시 시각장애인에 관심이 있으신가요?
Of course, I won't go on blind dates.
물론 소개팅은 안 할 거예요.
I see.
알겠어요.
You figured that out right away too.
너도 그걸 바로 알아냈지.
Then, can you tell me what I am feeling right now?
그럼 지금 내 기분이 어떤지 말해줄래?
No.
아니요.
But I want to know.
하지만 나는 알고 싶다.
You're someone whom I always want to get to know.
당신은 내가 항상 알고 싶은 사람입니다.
That's why I want to be with you.
그래서 나는 당신과 함께 있고 싶습니다.
I see.
알겠어요.
What?
무엇?
What do you mean by that?
그게 무슨 뜻이에요?
I'm saying that we should date.
우리 데이트하자고 말하는 거야.
♫ Everything about you  ♫
♫ 당신에 관한 모든 것 ♫
♫  oh everything about you ♫
♫ 오 당신에 관한 모든 것 ♫
♫ The moment our eyes met, they captured each other ♫
♫ 눈이 마주친 순간 서로를 사로잡았어 ♫
♫ Everything becomes love ♫
♫ 모든 것이 사랑이 됩니다 ♫
♫  oh everything becomes love ♫
♫ 오 모든 것이 사랑이 됩니다 ♫
♫ I wandered the universe ♫
♫ 나는 우주를 떠돌았어 ♫
♫  I found my earth ♫
♫ 내 지구를 찾았어 ♫
♫ Whether it's you or heaven  ♫
♫ 그것이 당신이든 천국이든 ♫
♫ Sometimes without my knowing why I become impatient ♫
♫ 가끔은 왜 나도 모르게 조급해지지 ♫
♫ Show me how you feel ♫
♫ 기분이 어떤지 보여주세요 ♫
♫ My heart is about to explode ♫
♫ 가슴이 터질 것 같아 ♫
♫  when I'm with you ♫
♫ 내가 너와 함께 있을 때 ♫
♫ Everything is made to match you ♫
♫ 모든 것이 당신에게 어울리도록 만들어졌습니다 ♫
♫ Everything about you ♫
♫ 당신에 관한 모든 것 ♫
♫ oh everything about you ♫
♫ 오 당신에 관한 모든 것 ♫
♫ The moment our eyes met, they captured each other ♫
♫ 눈이 마주친 순간 서로를 사로잡았어 ♫
Yumi's Cells 2 Preview
유미의 세포들 2 미리보기
Aren't you getting in?
안 들어가나요?
Go on ahead, I...
계속하세요. 저는...
Aren't you going to lunch?
점심 먹으러 안 가?
I still have some work to do.
아직 해야 할 일이 있어요.
You don't have a girlfriend.
당신은 여자 친구가 없습니다.
There must be someone he likes.
그 사람이 좋아하는 사람이 분명 있을 거예요.
Can you wait for me?
나를 기다려 줄 수 있나요?
We can't do anything without Love's permission.
사랑의 허락 없이는 아무것도 할 수 없습니다.
I hope the bus doesn't come.
버스가 안 왔으면 좋겠다.
♫ yeah yeah yeah ♫
♫ 그래 그래 그래 ♫
I'm starting to notice things I didn't notice before.
이전에는 눈치 채지 못했던 것들이 보이기 시작했습니다.
♫ I can feel you even when I close my eyes ♫
♫ 눈을 감아도 네가 느껴져 ♫
♫ whether it's you or heaven ♫
♫ 그것이 당신이든 천국이든 ♫